<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Lifecycle 404</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lifecycle 404</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.150.0</generator>
    <language>EN</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 02:01:47 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Audax 150KM Jakarta: Unsupported and Unbroken</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/go-blog/audax-150km-jakarta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 02:01:47 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/go-blog/audax-150km-jakarta/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I signed up for the Jakarta 150 KM audax thinking it would be a vibe—steady pace, friendly checkpoints, maybe an iced kopi at halfway. Instead, the sun clocked in early and refused to clock out. By kilometer 20 the heat was pinning me to the asphalt, every pedal stroke a reminder that I could tap out any time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The route didn’t help. Whoever traced the GPX must love chaos because the course dove into muddy backroads that grabbed at tires and shoes like quicksand. My drivetrain protested until the chain finally snapped, a metallic &lt;em&gt;thunk&lt;/em&gt; that rattled me harder than any climb. I patched it together with greasy fingers and a spare link, cursing every puddle hiding jagged gravel.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Ramadan Reflection ~ 😅 Late Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/go-blog/ramadan-reflections/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 11:21:14 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/go-blog/ramadan-reflections/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ramadhan-stories&#34;&gt;Ramadhan Stories&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few months back, around Ramadan, I stumbled into an anime I totally misjudged.&lt;br&gt;
Thought it was some weird horror or action thing (title had &lt;em&gt;Orb&lt;/em&gt; in it, so yeah, I expected punching or blood or something like that).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turns out&amp;hellip; it was about &lt;strong&gt;geocentric vs. heliocentric theory&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
Earth-centered vs. Sun-centered.&lt;br&gt;
And the madness people faced when they tried to prove something the world wasn’t ready to accept.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Bike, Dumber Owner  🤦‍♂️🚲</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/go-blog/idiot-bike-idiot-owner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 02:15:14 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/go-blog/idiot-bike-idiot-owner/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It all started with &lt;strong&gt;Patrick&lt;/strong&gt; —&lt;br&gt;
Not a person. A bike.&lt;br&gt;
A &lt;em&gt;junk Chinese gravel bike&lt;/em&gt; I bought for &lt;strong&gt;600K&lt;/strong&gt; from the cursed depths of &lt;strong&gt;Shitpee&lt;/strong&gt; (yeah, &lt;del&gt;Shopee&lt;/del&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before it was Patrick, it was just&amp;hellip; tragic.&lt;br&gt;
White frame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shitty red decals&lt;/strong&gt; that looked like knock-off fire graphics.&lt;br&gt;
I thought stickers would save it.&lt;br&gt;
So I went full Jaksel-core: anime, fake brands, nonsense logos.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;It looked worse.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I don’t know why…&lt;br&gt;
I &lt;em&gt;loved&lt;/em&gt; that damn bike.&lt;br&gt;
Maybe because it didn’t care what it looked like.&lt;br&gt;
It just kept rolling — no questions asked.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Found Myself</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/go-blog/how-i-found-myself/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 01:10:46 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/go-blog/how-i-found-myself/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-it-wasnt-what-i-expected&#34;&gt;Why It Wasn’t What I Expected&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For as long as I can remember, I thought life was supposed to follow a straight line. You pick a dream when you’re young—astronaut, architect, rockstar, whatever—and then you chase it down, step by step. That’s what we’re told, anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But here’s what nobody tells you: most of us end up &lt;em&gt;somewhere completely different&lt;/em&gt;. We blink, years pass, and suddenly we’re not the people we once imagined.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pertama</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/go-blog/celotehan-bego-pertama/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 01:57:03 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/go-blog/celotehan-bego-pertama/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-dont-even-know-where-to-start&#34;&gt;I don’t even know where to start.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe this blog exists out of ego. Maybe it’s just me trying to fix the mess I made with rasastroberi—a blog I once loved, hated, and at one point thought about killing (along with the part of me that made it). Or maybe it’s an attempt to bury alkind_COOL—a name so cringe I still flinch thinking about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;anyway-im-glad-youre-here&#34;&gt;Anyway… I’m glad you&amp;rsquo;re here.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This space, agungsukariman.com, is gonna be my place to dump thoughts. I’ll talk about digital marketing, tech stuff, dead or dying SEO tricks, tools I like, music I listen to, things I’m building, breaking, or obsessed with. Nothing too formal. Just notes from my head to yours.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/promise-me-you-will-make-a-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 10:10:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/promise-me-you-will-make-a-call/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Got something to say? Whether it’s serious or just for fun, I’m all ears.&lt;br&gt;
If you’re dealing with a tracking issue on the client side, setting up GA4, wrestling with server-side tagging, or your DataLayer looks like spaghetti 🍝 — let me know your stack. I’ll help. Promise. 🤝&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can email me at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:agungsukariman.com&#34;&gt;agungsukariman@gmai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
or drop a message through the contact form below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I usually reply within 1×24 hours ⏳ — unless my Wi-Fi decides to ghost me 👻.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long Story Short</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/let-me-tell-you-a-stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 10:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/let-me-tell-you-a-stories/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The truth is, &lt;em&gt;Agung&lt;/em&gt; was never meant to be my name. My mom wanted &lt;em&gt;Agus&lt;/em&gt; — you know, the classic Indo name, mass-produced like mie instan 🍜. But maybe that’s the problem. Too many &lt;em&gt;Agus&lt;/em&gt;es walking around. So my dad came through with &lt;em&gt;Agung&lt;/em&gt;. Sounds like some Bali prince or gamelan prodigy… but nope. Just me. Not Balinese. Just… here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sukariman&lt;/em&gt;? That’s a whole other drama.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SU&lt;/strong&gt; from &lt;em&gt;Sulastri&lt;/em&gt;, my mom — the real MVP.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;KARIM&lt;/strong&gt;, from the Karim family, who literally picked baby me up from the hospital when my parents were broke. No grab, no gojek, just pure kindness ❤️&lt;br&gt;
And &lt;strong&gt;MAN&lt;/strong&gt;? That’s for &lt;em&gt;Basman&lt;/em&gt;, my dad. Or as I like to call it… &lt;em&gt;Bestman&lt;/em&gt;. Lols.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
